告诉你吧 罗斯 她要你
I'm telling you, Ross, she wants you.
她基本不认识我 我们只是住在同一栋楼里
She barely knows me. We just live in the same building.
有过来往吗?      她曾经借过我一个蛋
Any contact?        She lent me an egg once.
你有机会了
You're in.
对啊
Oh, right.
罗斯      嗨
Hey, Ross.        Hey.
快 罗斯 你该回到情场来
Come on, Ross. You gotta get back in the game here, ok?
和瑞秋的事儿没希望 前妻是同性恋
The Rachel thing's not happening, your exwife's a lesbian.
不想再有第三次了吧
I don't think we need a third.
麻烦可以给我们一个蛋吗 整个蛋 谢谢
Excuse me. Could we get an egg over here, still in the shell? Thanks.
蛋?
An egg?
对 你上前去跟她说 我来给你还鸡蛋
Yeah. You're gonna go up to her and say, "Here's your egg back. I'm returning your egg."
我们会赢的
I think it's winning.
我觉得这很不靠谱      她会喜欢的
I think it's insane.        She'll love it.
谢谢      谢谢 拿去
Thank you.        Thank you. Here.
带着蛋去吧 朋友
Go with the egg, my friend.
去啊 去 去
Go, go, go.
你觉得会成功吗?
Think it'll work?
不可能 这是自杀 有一个蛋的男人
No way. It's suicide. The man's got an egg.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第01季 第14集
情人节糖果 The One With the Candy Hearts
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：悠悠慕雪
你不可以这样      怎样?不可以怎样?
You can not do this.        Do what? Do what?
罗杰明晚要约她出去
Roger wants to take her out tomorrow night.
菲比 不行 你难道忘了当初为什么甩了他?
No. Pheebs. Don't you remember why you dumped the guy?
因为他很惹人厌又怪异
Because he was creepy.
还刻薄 还让人有点害怕
And mean. And a little frightening.
但情人节有伴总比没有好
Alright, still, it's nice to have a date on Valentine's Day.
大家好      好
Hi.        Hi.
菲比 你想和怪异男约会随时都可以
But Phoebe, you can go out with a creep any night of the year.
我会这样做
I know I do.
好      好
Hi.        Hi.
明晚你们有什么安排?
Well, what are you doing tomorrow night?
实际上 明晚的安排取决于今晚的表现
Actually, tomorrow night kinda depends on how tonight goes.
关于今晚      不 不 你不能背叛我
Oh. Uh, listen, about tonight        No, no, don't you dare bail on me.
她答应跟我约会的唯一原因
The only reason she's going out with me
就是我答应帮她朋友找伴
because I said I could bring a friend for her friend.
我知道 但她朋友听来似乎是个
Yes, I know. But her friend sounds like such a
可怜虫 我知道 但是
pathetic mess. I know, but
好啦 老兄 她如此渴望 如此脆弱
Come on, man, she's needy, she's vulnerable.
我想呢
I'm thinking
谢了
Thanks.
你和珍妮丝分手后就没约会过 你一定要去
Look, you haven't been out with a woman since Janice. You're doing this.
嗨      嗨
Hi.        Hi.
她答应了      哈
She said yes.        Ahem.
干得好
Yes! Way to go, man.
蛋还在身上?      对
Still got the egg, huh?        Yeah.
我看起来怎样?      额
How do I look?        Oh, urn...
我不关心
I don't care.
洛莲来了
There's Lorraine.
记住 不准交换
Ok, now, remember, no trading.
漂亮的给你 悲惨的给我
You get the pretty one. I get the mess.
嗨 乔伊      嗨
Hi, Joey.        Hey.
瞧瞧
Well well.
看看你带了什么人来
Look what you brought.
真棒
Very nice.
看看你带了谁?
And what did you bring?
她还在寄放外套
She's checking her coat.
乔伊 我要去洗手 把出租车的味儿洗掉
Joey, I'm gonna go wash the cab smell off of my hands.
你能帮我点杯白葡萄酒
Will you get me a white Zinfandel
帮珍妮丝点杯红葡萄酒好吗?
and a glass of red for Janice?
珍妮丝?
Janice?
哦
Oh...
我的
my
天啊
God.
是珍妮丝
Hey, it's Janice.
我要逃走 从窗户逃出去
Okay, I'm making a break for it. I'm going out the window.
不不不 拜托了 我一直想约洛莲很久很久了
No,no, no, don't, please. I've been waiting for like, forever to go out with Lorraine.
冷静点      冷静?冷静?
Just calm down.        Calm down? Calm down?
你居然帮我和一个五个月内
You set me up with a woman
被我甩过两次的女人牵红线
I've dumped twice in the last five months.
嗨
Hey.
别对我嚷嚷好吗 你让我紧张
Can you stop yelling? You're making me nervous.
我一紧张就尿不出来
And I can't go when I'm nervous.
抱歉 你说的没错
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You're right.
快点! 快! 快! 尿啊!
Come on! Do it, do it, do it! Come on!
好啦 罗杰是很怪 但跟皮特卡尼比起来不算什么
Okay, Roger was creepy, but he was nothing compared to Pete Carney.
皮特卡尼谁?      爱哭鬼皮特?
Which one was Pete Carney?        Pete the Weeper?
还记得每次做爱都会哭的家伙吗?
Remember the guy who used to cry every time we had sex?
"你舒服吗?"
"Oh was it good for you?"
好吧 我每天都想替霍华德哭 那个"我赢了"家伙
Yeah, well, I'll take a little crying any day over Howard, the "I win" guy.
"我赢了 我赢了"
"I win. I win."
和他约会两个月 我一次都没赢过
I went out with him for two months. I didn't get to win once.
我们这些良家妇女 怎会跟这些混蛋在一起呢?
How did we end up with these jerks?  We're good people.
不知道 可能是我们有某种吸引力吧
I don't know. Maybe we're some kind of magnets.
我知道我有 所以我才不能戴电子表
I know I am. That's why I can't wear a digital watch.
还有啤酒 对吧?
There's more beer, right?
记得我那剃光头的朋友艾比吗?
Oh. You know my friend Abby who shaves her head?
她说如果想要打破与恶男交往的恶性循环
She said that if you want to break the bad boyfriend cycle
可以举行一个清理仪式
you can do like a cleansing ritual.
菲比 这女人自愿变成秃头啊
Pheebs, this woman is voluntarily bald.
是啊
Yeah.
我们可以明天晚上试试
So we can do it tomorrow night, you guys.
情人节 非常合适
It's Valentine's Day. It's perfect.
仪式具体是怎样的呢?
Okay, well, what kind of ritual?
嗯 我们可以烧掉他们送的东西
Okay, we can, urn, we can burn the stuff they gave us.
或?
Or?
或者可以念经 裸体跳舞 拿着木棍
Or we can chant and dance around naked, you know, with sticks.
还是烧东西比较好      烧东西比较好
Burning's good.        Burning's good.
你知道
You know
自从我小时候 我就有办法用脚趾捡硬币
ever since I was little, I've been able to pick up quarters with my toes.
是吗? 真厉害
Yeah? Good for you.
几枚硬币 还是整捆硬币?
Uh, quarters or rolls of quarters?
对了 钱德 我把照片上的你都剪掉了
By the way, Chandler, I cut you out of all my pictures.
如果你想要的话 我有一整袋你的头
So if you want, I have a bag with just your heads.
不用了
That's okay.
确定? 真的? 你可以拿来做成小玩偶
Are you sure? Really? Because you know, you could make little puppets out of them.
然后放在你的"残酷剧院"里
And you could use them in your Theater of Cruelty.
不能这样
We can't do that.
哈? 不能怎样?
What? What can't you do?
能和你谈谈么? 到那边?
Uh, can I talk to you for a second? Over there?
我们估计得先走了
Uh, we might be leaving now.
告诉我这是你和我的我们
Tell me it's "you and me" we.
她说她想在我全身涂满东西 然后舔掉
She said she wants to slather my body with stuff and then lick it off.
我甚至不确定涂是什么意思
I'm not even sure what slathering is.
但我绝对不想错过
But I definitely want to be a part of it.
你不能这样对我
Okay, you can not do this to me.
你说的对 对不起 你是对的
You're right. I'm sorry. You're right.
三个巧克力慕斯外带好吗?
Uh. Can we have three chocolate mousses to go, please?
我要走了
I'm out of here.
这是我的信用卡 这顿算我的 对不起钱德
Here's my credit card. Dinner's on me. I'm sorry, Chandler.
希望她吐在你身上
I hope she throws up on you.
谢了
Thanks.
那么      就我们俩了
So        Just us.
多么糟糕的一晚
Ugh, what a crappy night.
但我还挺乐意欣赏 额 你的衬衫出来了
Although I have enjoyed the fact that, uh, your shirt's been sticking out
从你的拉链里 自从你从洗手间回来后
of your zipper ever since you came back from the bathroom.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你们好
How you doing?
他们是我们最好的朋友?
So do we have the best friends, or what?
乔伊算不上朋友 他是...
Joey's not a friend. He's...
把信用卡留给我们的笨蛋
a stupid man who left us his credit card.
再来一杯? 甜点? 大银幕电视?
Another drink? Some dessert? A big screen TV?
再来一杯吧
I will go for that drink.
没问题 好女人
You got it. Good woman.
来一瓶你们这最贵的香槟
Could we get a bottle of your most overpriced champagne?
每人一瓶      没错 每人一瓶
Each.        That's right. Each.
再来一瓶罗伯洛伊
Oh. And a, uh, Rob Roy.
我一直很好奇那是什么
I've always wanted to know.
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day.
我已经开始想你了
Oh I miss you already.
你能相信会发生这种事吗?
Can you believe this happened?
不 不
No, no.
但确实发生了
And yet it did.
再见 珍妮丝      吻我
Goodbye, Janice.        Kiss me.
钱德 抱歉
Oh, Chandler. Sorry.
嘿 珍妮丝      你好 摩妮卡
Hey, Janice.        Hi Monica.
这真是太特别了
Okay. Well, this was very special.
瑞秋 快看谁来了
Rach. Come see who's out here.
怎么了? 天啊
What's going on? Oh, my God.
珍妮丝 你好
Janice. Hi.
珍妮丝要走了
Janice is gonna go away now.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
乔伊 看谁来了
Oh. Joey. Look who it is.
哇奥
Whoa.
很好 乔伊回来了
Oh, good. Joey's home now.
这真是太好玩了
This is so much fun.
就像在走廊大团圆
This is like a reunion in the hall.
罗斯 跟某人打个招呼吧
Hi, hi, Ross. Yeah. There's someone I want you to say hi to.
他刚好打电话来
He just happened to call.
罗斯 对 是我 你怎么知道的?
Hello Ross. Yes, that's right. It's me. How did you know?
我只是说如果狗有时差
I'm just saying if dogs do experience jet lag, then
那么人的一岁是狗的七岁
because of the whole, uh, seven dog years to one human year thing
当狗从纽约飞到洛杉矶时
then, when a dog flies from New York to Los Angeles
他不是损失了三小时 而是一个半星期
he doesn't just lose three hours, he loses, like, a week and a half.
真有趣      对
That's funny.        Yeah.
怎么了?
What?
他们是谁?
Who are they?
额 金发的是我前妻
The, uh, blond woman is my exwife.
摸她的是她
And the woman touching her is her...
密友
close personal friend.
你是指她们是情侣吗?
You mean they're lovers?
如果你非得这么说的话
If you want to put a label on it.
哇哦
Wow. Heh.
还有什么我要知道的么      没了 就这么多
Anything else I should know?        Nope. That's it.
哦 还有她怀了我的孩子
Oh, and she's pregnant with my baby.
我总是忘了这部分
I always forget that part.
你们好
Hello.
好 现在我们需要鼠尾草和圣酒
Okay. So now we need, urn, sage branches and the sacramental wine.
我只有牛至叶和佛瑞斯加
All I have is, is oregano and a Fresca.
那也行
Urn, that's okay.
哦      好的
Ooh.         Okay.
好了 现在需要正义男人的精液
All right. Now we need the semen of a righteous man.
菲比 如果我们有 也就不需要做这个仪式了
Okay, Pheebs, you know what, if we had that, we wouldn't be doing the ritual in the first place.
可以开始丢东西了吗?      额 可以了
Can we just start throwing things in?        Urn, yeah, okay.
哦 额
Oh. Okay. Urn...
巴瑞的信
Okay. Barry's letters.
亚当瑞特的四角裤
Adam Ritter's boxer shorts.
我有和纳可努努晚餐的收据
And I have the receipt for my dinner with Nokululu ohh ah ah
看 史考特贾德的裸照      让我看看
Look, here's a picture of Scotty Jared naked.        Let me see.
他穿了毛衣
Hey he's wearing a sweater.
没有 哦!
No. Ew!
这是保罗剩下的葡萄酒
Okay, and here we have the last of Paolo's grappa.
等等 这不是几乎纯酒精的?
Wait. Isn't that stuff almost pure?
我怎么可以在情人节甩了她
How can I dump this woman on Valentine's Day?
不知道 但你新年就甩过她
I don't know. You dumped her on New Year's.
老兄 我下辈子要当马桶刷
Oh, man. In my next life, I'm coming back as a toilet brush.
你好 有趣的情人
Hello, funny valentine.
嗨 只是珍妮丝
Hi, just Janice.
你好 乔伊 我们的小媒人
Hello, Joey, our little matchmaker
我忍不住要吻你 我就要来
I could just kiss you all over, and I'm gonna.
要是你不敢 那我来
If you don't do it, I will.
你做什么工作?
So, urn, what do you do for a living?
过去几年我都在
Well, urn, for the past few years I've been working
哦不 我以为你说没有你他们可以自己做
Oh, no. I thought you said they could shoot the spot without you.
我以为他们可以
I thought they could.
和孩子们一起工作 真的很充实
working with children, which is really fulfilling.
我会尽快回来 对不起
I'll try to get back as soon as I can. I'm sorry.
我大部分时间是在教科学
So I'm spending most of my time teaching science, heh
有趣的是 那其实不是我的主修课程
which is funny because, that wasn't even my major
真有趣
Now, that is funny.
你觉得
Hey, do you think
我邀请卡萝过来会奇怪么?
Would it be too weird if I invited Carol over to join us?
因为 因为她现在一个人
Because she's, she's alone now.
又怀孕了 心情又不好
And pregnant. And sad.
应该可以吧      真的?
I guess.        Are you sure?
太好了 卡萝
Great. Carol.
要一起过来坐吗?
Wanna come over and join us?
不用 我没事
Oh, no.I'm fine. I'm fine.
来吧 过来 大家可以挪一下 过来
Come on, stand up. These people will scooch down. Come on.
过来坐 你们会挪过去一点 对吧
Come over here. You guys will scooch, won't you?
各位挪一下位置 拜托
Let's try scooching. Come on.
动起来      谢谢
Come on.        Thank you.
克莉丝汀丽格 这位是卡萝威利克
Uh, Kristen Riggs, this is Carol Willet.
卡萝 克莉丝汀      你好
Carol, Kristen.        How do you do?
你好
Hi
卡萝教六年级
Urn, Oh, uh, Carol teaches sixth grade.
克莉丝汀
And, uh, Kristen...
克莉丝汀的工作是...
Kristen does something
有趣的是...
that, funnily enough
不是她的主修
wasn't even her major.
里面有什么?
What do we got there?
一条四角裤
A piece of something, boxer shorts
明信片
greeting cards
还有烧得半焦的照片
and what looks like a half charred picture of
哇哦 这家伙的体毛比队长还多
Wow, that guy's hairier than the chief.
这件事说来好笑
You know, it's a really funny story how this happened.
没关系 你们不用解释
It's all right. It's all right. You don't have to explain.
这不是我们第一次营救失控的男友营火晚会
This isn't the first boyfriend bonfire that we've seen get out of control.
这已经是今晚第三件      真的?
You're our third call tonight.        Really?
当然 情人节一向是一年中最忙的晚上
Oh sure. Valentine's is our busiest night of the year.
我给你带了东西
I brought you something.
装子弹了吗?
Is it loaded?
哦 心形糖果
Oh, little candy hearts.
"永远的钱与珍"
"Chan and Jan forever"
我定做的
I had them made special.
好了 珍妮丝
Okay, Janice.
珍妮丝
Janice.
Hey, Janice.
我不知道怎么跟你说
Look, there's no way for me to tell you this.
至少没有新的办法来跟你说
At least, there's no new way for me to tell you this.
我觉得我们不会有结果
I just don't think things are gonna work out.
没关系
That's fine.
真的吗?      嗯哼
It is?        Mmhm.
因为我知道我们没结束
Because I know that this isn't the end.
不 事实上 结束了
Oh, no. You see, actually, it is.
不 没有 因为你不会让它发生
No, it isn't. Because you won't let that happen.
你到现在还不明白吗?
Don't you know it yet?
你爱我 钱德宾
You love me, Chandler Bing.
不 我不爱
Oh, no, I don't.
那你问问你自己 我们为什么总是会在一起
Well then ask yourself this. why do you think we keep ending up together?
新年 谁邀请谁?
New Year's, who invited who?
情人节 谁邀请谁上床?
Valentine's, who asked who into whose bed?
都是我 但是...      你找的我
I did, but        You seek me out.
你内心深处呼唤我 就像雾中的号角
Something deep in your soul calls out to me like a foghorn.
珍妮丝 珍妮丝
Janice. Janice.
你想要我 你需要我
You want me. You need me.
没有我你活不下去
You can't live without me.
而且你知道
And you know it.
只是你自己不知道你知道
You just don't know you know it.
再见
See you.
打电话给我
Call me.
这不是真的 我从没说你妈是狼人
It's not true. I never called your mother a wolverine.
你有 我发誓 真的有
You did so. I swear I swear to.
她去洗手间多久了?
How long has she been in the bathroom?
我想她不在洗手间 她外套不见了
Uh I don't think she's in the bathroom. Her coat is gone.
可能是因为里面冷
Well, maybe it's cold in there.
或者是我毁了九年来第一次约会
Or maybe I screwed up the first date I had in nine years.
可能就是这样      天啊
That could be it.        Oh, God.
这里还是很烫
You know, this is still pretty hot.
蘑菇
Mushroom.
笑一个
Smile.
她们不会都这样的 有些女人会吃完晚餐的
They won't all be like this. Some women might even stay through dinner.
抱歉 不好笑      不 只是
I'm sorry. That's not funny.        No, it's just
你知道 人们总说"继续你的人生"
Well, you know the whole "getting on with your life" thing?
我一定要这样吗?
Well, do I have to?
我和这位美女坐在一起
I mean, well, I'm sitting here with this cute woman
她人很好
and she's perfectly nice, you know?
但是
But that there's
就没有然后了
That's it.
但和你聊天 轻松 有趣
And, uh, then I'm here talking to you, and it's easy and it's fun.
我不 不需要
And I don't, I don'thave to...
我懂      你懂?
I know.        You know?
我有个疯狂的想法 额
Here's a wacky thought. Urn, ahem.
我们再试一次好么      罗斯
What's say you and I give it another shot.        Ross.
不 不 我知道你想说什么 你是女同
No, no, I know what you're gonna say. You're a lesbian.
我们暂时把那搁下怎样?
But what do you say we just put that aside for now, you know?
把它先放在一边 好吗?
Let's just stick a pin in it, okay?
因为我们在一起很好
Because we're great together, you know?
你不能否认
You can't deny it.
而且 你还怀着我的宝宝
And besides, you're carrying my baby.
这不是很完美吗?      罗斯
I mean, how perfect is that?        Ross
你一直这样说 但有件事却没变
You keep saying that, but there's something right here.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
但      没有但是 没有但是
But        No but. No but.
你知道这件我们暂时放在一边的事会怎样么?
You know that thing you put over here with the pin in it?
迟早会出现的
It's time to take the pin out.
好吧
Yeah.
你会找到某个人 一定会 那个人在等着你
You'll find someone. I know you will. The right woman is just waiting for you.
你说的简单 你已经找到那个人了
That's easy for you to say. You found one already.
所有你需要的是一个喜欢男人的女人
All you need is a woman who likes men
然后就可以了
and you'll be set.
不是她
Not her.
我们午夜下班 然后过来接你们怎样?
We get off around midnight. Why don't we pick you up then?
好      好
Okay.        Great.
那你们会开消防车来吗?
So, urn will you bring the truck?
还会让你拉警铃      哇哦!
I'll even let you ring the bell.        Wahoo!
晚点见      晚点见
We'll see you later. Bye.        See you later.
谢谢 再见
Thanks. See you.
天啊
Oh, my God.
看 这不就有了吗?
See, there you go.
清理仪式奏效了      真的
The cleansing works.        You're right.
他们都是好人
They're nice guys.
是消防队员
Oh. They're firemen guys.
你们跟她们说你们结婚了么?      绝不说
You guys tell them you were married?        No way.
你开玩笑么 我女朋友都不知道 我才不会说
Are you kidding? My girlfriend doesn't know. I'm not gonna tell them.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
海盗编号：HDT14-P1-24-14-01-1212